Ow! It's eating my face!
(Raj:)It's eating his face!
(Sheldon(throwing alien onto the laptop):)I found your webcam
and replaced the video feed.
(Sheldon(throwing alien onto the laptop):)You two should be ashamed of yourselves.
- Sheldon, we're really sorry.
- Yeah, really sorry.
(Sheldon:)Sorry?
(Sheldon:)You may not realize it, but I have difficulty
navigating certain aspects of daily life.
(Sheldon:)You know, understanding sarcasm.
Feigning interest in others.
(Sheldon:)Not talking about trains
as much as I want to.
(Sheldon:)It's exhausting.
Which is why, for 20 minutes a day,
I like to go down to that room...
(Sheldon:)...turn my mind off,
and do what I need to do to recharge.
(Howard:)But what are you doing in there?
And what does 43 mean?
(Sheldon:)You don't need to know,
you don't deserve to know...
(Sheldon:)...and you will never know.
(Raj:)Yeah, well, I know how to make
your egg salad now.